More fun than you can shake your stick at!
Loose Screws is a comedy film directed by Rafal Zielinski.
What happens when four high school screw-ups are forced to
attend an academy summer school to graduate?
They turn their scholastic sentence into a wacky game
of trying to improve their scores...
with the women.
The ultimate conquest for the 100-point prize is the sexy new French teacher, but
she proves to be a bigger challenge than their failing grades.
The unforgiving principal foils every scheme, and their sidesplitting
last chance is the academy's anniversary celebration.
Brad Lovett, played by Bryan Genesse.
Steve Hardman, played by Lance Van Der Kolk.
Hugh G. Rection, played by Alan Deveau.
Marvin Eatmore, played by Jason Warren.
Mona Lott, played by Cynthia Belliveau.
Principal Arsenault, played by Mike MacDonald.
Screwballs II, also known as Loose Screws, is a
1985 Canadian teen sex comedy film.
It is a sequel to Screwballs and was one of the first
releases from Roger Corman's Concorde Pictures.
The film explores themes of cheerleader, bikini, sequel, sex comedy, voyeur.
The tone is lighthearted.